http://cmsreport.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Dakota Imagery Group collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Dakota Imagery Group’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Dakota Imagery Group’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Dakota Imagery Group may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Dakota Imagery Group also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on socpub.com articles. Dakota Imagery Group only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Dakota Imagery Group’s websites choose to interact with Dakota Imagery Group in ways that require Dakota Imagery Group to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Dakota Imagery Group gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask article contributors who sign up to post an article at socpub.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, Dakota Imagery Group collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Dakota Imagery Group. Dakota Imagery Group does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Dakota Imagery Group may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Dakota Imagery Group may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Dakota Imagery Group does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Dakota Imagery Group discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Dakota Imagery Group’s behalf or to provide services available at Dakota Imagery Group’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Dakota Imagery Group’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Dakota Imagery Group will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Dakota Imagery Group discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Dakota Imagery Group believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Dakota Imagery Group, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Dakota Imagery Group website and have supplied your email address, Dakota Imagery Group may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Dakota Imagery Group and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Dakota Imagery Group takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Dakota Imagery Group uses cookies to help socpub.com identify and track visitors, their usage of the website, and their website access preferences. socpub.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Dakota Imagery Group’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Dakota Imagery Group’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If socpub.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Dakota Imagery Group goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of socpub.com may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Dakota Imagery Group and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Dakota Imagery Group may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Dakota Imagery Group’s sole discretion. Dakota Imagery Group encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a socpub.com account, you should also check the site's privacy page for these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Latest
National Center for Missing & Exploited Children assessment of Cyan Tech finds it can help “safeguard children”
Dec 10, 2020 - 08:37
Increase in online shopping accelerating race for customer loyalty, research finds
Dec 10, 2020 - 06:46
Network attacks hit two-year high during pandemic despite shift to remote working
Dec 9, 2020 - 05:15
2020 Tech Trailblazers Award winners announced
Dec 8, 2020 - 09:59
5 Digital Transformation-Driven Cybersecurity Considerations
Dec 8, 2020 - 06:47
More
Promotions
Most Popular
How Apple is Using Big DataTechnology
Confirmit Named a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Voice of the CustomerInformation Technology
Kameleoon Included as New Entrant in Experience Optimization Platform Evaluation by Independent Research FirmInformation Technology
Bryan Ruby's Blog
Are my vinyl records worth millions?The Great Cycle Challenge - Final DaysThe Great Cycle Challenge - Week 3 & 4The Great Cycle Challenge - Week 2American Flag and Labor DayMore
Copyright © 2020, socPub - Dakota Imagery Group and contributors.
